<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

 <title>Sidey</title>
 <link href="http://localhost:4000/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
 <link href="http://localhost:4000/"/>
 <updated>2020-05-08T01:16:33-04:00</updated>
 <id>http://localhost:4000</id>
 <author>
   <name></name>
   <email></email>
 </author>

 
 <entry>
   <title>The Beginning</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/2020/05/07/the-beginning"/>
   <updated>2020-05-07T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/2020/05/07/the-beginning</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;        The true gift of being able to program is the same as an artist, in fact, I would consider programming an art. The work of art is displayed through the screen, the artist is the programmer and the audience are the people viewing the work through the screen. In the summer of fifth grade, I was bored and searched for “How to create a custom website” on YouTube. I found a video that had no sound was a video on a person typing the basic elements saved the file and refreshed the browser to showcase what it did. I was very intrigued by this and that summer I spent all day and night teaching myself how to do this because for as long as I can remember I have always thought that having something custom would lead to success rather than just downloading a popular template. Ever since I have entertained myself by teaching myself and being curious. I have taught myself a bit of everything; Java to create custom plugins for a Minecraft server, I have also dabbled into some PHP to learn the backend of websites, JavaScript for the front-end of websites, C Sharp for Unity, and Python which I have currently just gotten into.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;        The biggest thing I have gotten from programming as of today is to always be curious and never stop looking for the answers and facts that are on your mind. I have noticed that the best programmers are always asking questions and that the main objective of one is to solve a problem.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 

</feed>
